

ABOUT ME

Freelance Web and Mobile developer Developer specializing in Full-stack development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects and mobile applications. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including React-native, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, Python, Java and Kotlin. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

KIKUYU

KISWAHILI

LINKS

Website:

http://del-ui.42web.io/

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wam bui-victor-263a84201/http://

Twitter:

https://twitter.com/del_ui

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth 30/09/2001

Nationality Kenyan

Visa status **Approved**

Marital status Single

REFERENCE

STEPHEN NGUJIRI Context Expert Agencies Limited **T**: 0794757292 E: villadev840@gmail.com

VICTOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER & A DATA SCIENTIST

Makongeni Phase 5, Thika, Kenya

0702826475

kamauvictor840@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

NJERU INDUSTRIES

Aug 2022

Network Engineer

Effectively managed the design and installation of all system networks. Tested, documented, and maintained all network components. Performed life cycle upgrades of network infrastructure. Researched and troubleshooted any network performance issues and worked to resolve them immediately. Maintained an inventory of networking equipment and supplies. Worked as a thoughtful and cooperative team member.

OMDENA

Nairobi Jun 2019 - Jan 2020 **Data Scientist**

Worked at these great companies for two months and gained some exposure to Machine learning and Al. Company Kaggle company Omdena Duration - [2021] company - Nairobi - Kenya

SECTION ENGINEERING EDUCATION

Silicon Valley Jul 2021 - Present **Technical Writer**

Worked as a technical writer, writing computer science articles in different CS disciplines

EDUCATION

MERU UNIVERSITY

Meru

2023

Computer Engineering

Bachelor of Science

NYANGWA BOYS Embu

2018

KSCE

SKILLS

PHP (SCRIPTING LANGUAGE)

SQL (PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE)

REACT NATIVE

MACHINE LEARNING

JAVA, KOTLIN (ANDROID DEVELOPMENT)

INTERNSHIPS

NJERU INDUSTRIES

Makutano, Meru May 2022 - Aug 2022

CONTEXT EXPERT AGENCIES LIMITED

Nairobi Apr 2023 - Jun 2023 **ICT Specialist**

ICT Intern

HOBBIES

PLAYING COMPUTER GAMES

COURSE

MERU UNIVERSITY Jun 2019 - Apr 2023 Bsc in Computer Engineering

PUBLICATIONS

MACHINE LEARNING IMAGE

CLASSIFICATION Dec 2021

YOUTUBE VIDEO DOWNLOADER USING PYTHON

USING MONTE CARLO SIMULATION Oct 2021

Machine Learning Image Classification with Javascript and Nyckel

YouTube Video Downloader

Making Predictions Using Monte Carlo Simulation